fujicolor.eu 2016-05-31

# Privacy Policy | Fujifilm Europe

We at FUJIFILM Europe GmbH are pleased that you are visiting our [website ](https://www.fujifilm.eu/eu/products/digital-cameras/interchangeable-lens-cameras/model/x-m1-1)and thank you for the interest you have shown in our company, our products and our websites. It is important to us that your privacy is protected whilst using our websites. We collect, process and use personal data in accordance with the pertinent legal requirements, in particular with the Data Protection Directive 95/46/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 24 October 1995 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data and any revision thereof, the German Federal Data Protection Act (Bundesdatenschutzgesetz; BDSG), and the German Telemedia Act (Telemediengesetz; TMG). For this reason we ask that you please read the following information: 

### Collection and processing of personal data

In principle you can visit and use our website without telling us who you are. This does not require any registration - with the exception of the use of personalized data. Without further information from you we only collect and process the name of your Internet Service Provider, the webpage from which you came to us and the pages that you visit on our website. We do not collect your IP address. This information is only used for purposes of provision of our website and is then deleted. This data is also analyzed for statistical purposes, whereby you remain anonymous as an individual user. Personal data is only collected if you provide us with this information, for example in order to register for personalized services and only processed and used for the provision of these personalized services or in order to process your enquiries. Furthermore within the framework of the personalized services of FUJIFILM Europe GmbH we will only process and use your data for advertising and market research purposes or for demand-related provision of electronic services on condition that you have given your express electronic permission. Moreover in the event that you give your express electronic permission all the information accessed by you whilst visiting our websites will be edited into a user profile in order to be able to offer you information specifically personalized for you (e.g. in the form of a newsletter). You can access the content of your express electronic permission here at any time. You can of course also withdraw your permission here at any time with effect for the future. 

### Special terms of use for web tools / social media plug-ins

Various web tools (analysis programmes and social media services) have been integrated into the Internet site [www.fujifilm.eu](http://www.fujifilm.eu/), some of which function with the aid of “Cookies”. Cookies are text files that are sent by a web server to the user’s browser in order to store information on the user’s PC via the browser that is being used, for example the user’s current IP address and information about the user. The next time the web server is accessed, the applicable data regarding the user is transmitted from the Cookie file. 

If you wish, you can deactivate the use of cookies via your browser settings at any time. Please note, however, that in this case you may not be able to make full use of the complete range of functions offered by the website [www.fujifilm.eu.](http://www.fujifilm.eu/)

On the Internet site [www.fujifilm.eu](http://www.fujifilm.eu/), plug-ins for the following social networks have been or will be integrated (hereinafter collectively referred to as “networks” or “network”):

  * **AddThis** , operated by the company AddThis, LLC, 8000 Westpark Dr., Suite 625, McLean, VA 22102, USA (“AddThis”). Further information on data protection and data processing by AddThis as well as your options for settings and your rights can be viewed at [www.addthis.com/privacy](http://www.addthis.com/privacy).
  *  **facebook.com** , operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA (“Facebook”). The plug-ins are indicated with a Facebook logo (white “f” on a blue tile background a “Like” (thumbs up) symbol) or are identified with the addendum “Facebook social plug-in”. The list of Facebook social plug-ins and their appearance can be viewed at [www.facebook.com/policy.php](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php).
  *  **Twitter** , operated by Twitter, Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA (hereinafter referred to as “Twitter”). The plug-ins can be identified by the Twitter logo (bird outline/relief in various colours against various backgrounds). The various Twitter logos which are used to indicate the plug-in can be viewed on the Twitter website under [www.twitter.com/about/resources/logos](http://twitter.com/about/resources/logos).
  * “+1” button of the social network **Google Plus** , operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United States (“Google”). The button can be identified by the symbol “+1” against a white background. Further information about this can be found at [www.google.com/intl/policies/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/intl/policies/policies/privacy/).
  *  **Pinterest** \- Pinterest Trademark Agent, 635 High Street, Palo Alto, CA 94301 USA  
  *  **Youtube** \- YouTube, LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066 USA  
  *  **Digg.com -** Digg Inc. , 135 Mississippi St. , San Francisco, CA USA   
  *  **delicious.com** \- AVOS Systems, Inc.,  273 S. Railroad Ave., Suite A, San Mateo, CA 94401 USA  
  *  **XING -** XING AG, Gänsemarkt 43, 20354 Hamburg, Germany  
  *  **LinkedIn** \- LinkedIn Corporation, 2029 Stierlin Court, Mountain View, CA 94043 USA  

All of these network plug-ins essentially work according to the same basic principle as described in the following:

When you access [www.fujifilm.eu](http://www.fujifilm.eu/), these plug-ins can potentially create a direct connection between the user’s browser and the server of the respective network. The content of the plug-in will be directly transmitted from the network to your browser, which will integrate it into the website. We have no influence regarding the scope of the data which is collected with the aid of the plug-in. Therefore, we can only inform you about the information which is publically accessible according to our current state of knowledge (see above). The integrated plug-in informs the network that the user has accessed the website [www.fujifilm.eu](http://www.fujifilm.eu/) and informs the network of the user’s IP address. If the user is logged in to the network of this plug-in at that point in time, the network will be able to link the visit with the user’s account. 

If the user interacts with the plug-ins, for example in the case of Twitter by clicking on “Tweet This” or with Facebook by clicking the ‘I like’ button or making a comment, the corresponding information will be transmitted directly from the user’s browser to the network where it will then be stored. Furthermore, additional personal data may also be transmitted and stored there, for example the user’s IP address, personal browser settings and other parameters.

If you are a member of the respective network and do not want it to collect information about you via [www.fujifilm.eu](http://www.fujifilm.eu/) and to link this information with the data that the network has already stored about you, then please close this website, log out from your user account for the respective network and afterwards visit our website once again.

If you are not a member of the network or you have logged from the network before visiting our Internet site, the possibility still exists that the network will ascertain (at least) your IP address and store it. Please note that this information is already exchanged when you visit our Internet site under the [www.fujifilm.eu](http://www.fujifilm.eu/), regardless whether you interact with the plug-ins or not.

### Web statistics tools

#### Google Analytics

The website [www.fujifilm.eu](http://www.fujifilm.eu/) uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (“Google”). The information generated by the Google Analytics cookie about your usage of [www.fujifilm.eu](http://www.fujifilm.eu/), including your IP address, is transferred to a Google server in the USA, where it is saved. During this process, the _anonymizeIP() system is used to anonymize your IP address so that it cannot be attributed to your internet connection.

Google uses this information to evaluate your usage of the www.fujifilm.eu and to create website activity reports for the website operator, as well as to provide further services relating to the website and Internet usage. Google may also pass on this information to third parties if legally required or if it has contracted them to process the information. 

You can opt out from the gathering of data by the service Google Analytics with effect for the future by installing the “Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on” which is offered by Google. Further information on the service Google Analytics is available on the website page [www.google.com/intl/analytics/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/intl/analytics/policies/privacy/)

#### Data Security

FUJIFILM Europe GmbH takes all necessary technical and organizational security measures in order to protect your personal data from being abused and to prevent the loss of your data. Your personal data is saved in a secure operating environment that is not accessible to the public. All personal data provided by you in the course of registration or use of personal services will be transferred in encoded form in order to help prevent misuse of the data by a third party.  
Transfer, export and processing of the data in states outside the European Economic Area.

No transfer will take place to third parties such as companies within the Fujifilm Group and the data will not be exported to states outside the European Economic Area. 

#### External links

You can find more comprehensive information in links on our website that refer to the websites of third parties. In so far as this is not obviously recognizable please note with regard to such link that it is an external link. We have absolutely no influence on the content and design of the websites of these other providers. Thus this data protection declaration is obviously not valid for the websites of other providers.

Further information and contacts, information, corrections, blocking and deletion.

Should you have further questions on the topic of “Data protection at FUJIFILM Europe GmbH”, please contact the data protection officer at our company at the following contact address: 

FUJIFILM Europe GmbH, Datenschutzbeauftragte, Heesenstrasse 31,  
40549 Düsseldorf or dataprotection(at)fujifilm(dot)eu. 

You are entitled to free information on or correction, blocking or deletion of your stored data, including data stored under a pseudonym. Please contact the address given above by email or by mail. You can ask to receive the information in written form, otherwise in the form of an email.
